dorianyates.net 2017-05-31

# Privacy Policy at Dorian Yates Nutrition

### PRIVACY POLICY

Dorian Yates Nutrition respects the privacy of every individual who visits its Web Site. From time to time Dorian Yates Nutrition may collect data from you such as your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, comments and the like.

This privacy statement outlines the policies on what Dorian Yates Nutrition will do with the information it collects and gives you instructions on what to do if you want Dorian Yates Nutrition Inc to remove your personal information or if you have any questions concerning Dorian Yates Nutrition  privacy policy.

Use of Personal Information Dorian Yates Nutrition will not collect or keep any of your personal information (that is your name, postal address, e- mail address or telephone number) unless you provide it to Dorian Yates Nutrition voluntarily. If you do not want any personal information about you collected by Dorian Yates Nutrition please do not submit it. If you have already submitted this information and would like Dorian Yates Nutrition to remove it from its records please contact Dorian Yates Nutrition at the phone number listed at the bottom of this privacy statement.

Dorian Yates Nutrition will use reasonable efforts to delete your personal information from its existing files. Most importantly, at no time will Dorian Yates Nutrition sell, rent, or give any of your personal information to any third party. There are only two exceptions to this rule.

Information Collected Automatically To efficiently operate its Web Site, Dorian Yates Nutrition may collect certain technical information automatically when you visit Dorian Yates Nutrition Web Site. For example, such information may include the type of Internet Browser or operating system you are using and the name of the Web Site from you linked to Dorian Yates Nutrition Web Site. This information will not allow Dorian Yates Nutrition to identify you personally.

How We Use Email After you place an order on our site, you will receive an email confirmation and, in most cases, an email with order  information.

 **How to Contact Dorian Yates Nutrition**

If you have submitted information to Dorian Yates Nutrition through its Web Site and you would like Dorian Yates Nutrition to delete that information from its records please contact Dorian Yates Nutrition at sales@dorianyatesnutrition.com

†These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat or prevent any disease. Dorian Yates Nutrition does not condone the use of illegal anabolic steroids.

### COOKIE POLICY

Cookies are tiny text files stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages. We use cookies to enable the smooth use of our website, in some cases keep track of whats in your basket and track your visit using Google Analytics.

To use our website most effectively you need to have cookies enabled. If you decide to disable cookies you'll still be able to browse the site may encounter some issues. Most modern web browsers (Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Safari & Mozilla Firefox) come with Cookies enabled. If you wish to turn them off, simply look further down this article for a handy guide for each browser.

It's important to note that cookies don't harm your computer. We don't store any personal data in the cookies we create such as payment details, but we do use cookies to track analytical information to enable us to deliver a better service.

On the site you may see plugins to Facebook and Twitter feeds. These write a small cookie to your machine to enable us to bring you this additional information. If you wish to disable this you can do very easily via your browsers settings.

All this information is being passed to you as part of our ongoing initiative to comply with the new legislation being passed by the Information Commissioners Office (ICO). We want to be honest and clear about privacy and cookies when you're using our website.

**Cookie Policy**

You will be able to browse this website if you decide to disable cookies, but to make full use of it we think you should accept cookies. The most important cookie we use on the site is what's called a 'session cookie' The session cookie is written when you access the site but does nothing unless you login and wish to save your details for example.

However, if you would like to delete or block cookies from the website you can use your browser to do this. Each of the modern browsers are different so please view your browser or mobile device's help/manual to edit your cookie preferences.

Below you can find a list of the cookies we use and their use:

**Cookie Name** | **Purpose and use of Cookie**  
---|---  
CONCRETE5 | This cookie is a session cookie. This means that each time you visit our website it is created and when you leave our website it is removed. It enables our web server to respond to your actions on the site when viewing pages, blogs, logging into the website, making purchases. The website wouldn't work efficiently for you without it.  
__utma  
__utmb  
__utmc  
__utmv  
__utmx | This cookie enable the function of [Google Analytics Software](http://www.google.com/analytics/). This helps us take and analyse visitor information such as browser usage, new visitor numbers, response to marketing activity and visiting times. That information helps us to improve the website and your website experience, and to make our marketing campaigns relevant.

The data stored by these cookies can be seen only by our team and Google and **does not show or collect** any confidential information. For more information on Google Cookies, please see the [Google site](https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies#cookiesSet)  
  
__pref  
__visitor_info1_live | These cookies are set by the You tube video plugin that you may see around the site. If you deactivate them you may not be able to see the You Tube Videos.  
  
**Managing Cookies**

Most modern web browsers enable cookies by default. If cookies are not enabled on your computer your experience on our website may be limited in some areas.

To enable/disable cookies, please refer to your browsers help guide. We have some guidelines below on how to enable cookies on the most popular browsers:

| **Mozilla Firefox**  
Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser window and select Options. Then select the Privacy icon . Then click on Cookies, then select 'allow or disallow sites to set cookies'.  
---|---  
| **Google Chrome**  
Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser window and select Options . Then click the 'Under the Bonnet' tab, locate the 'Privacy' section, and select the 'Content settings' button, now select 'Allow local data to be set' or to turn off 'block sites from setting any data'  
| **Microsoft Internet Explorer 6.0, 7.0, 8.0, 9.0, 10.0, 11**  
Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser window and select 'Internet options' , then click on the 'Privacy' tab. Ensure that your Privacy level is set to Medium or below, which will enable cookies in your browser. Settings above Medium will disable cookies.  
| **Safari**  
Click on the Cog icon at the top of your browser window and select the 'Preferences' option. Then click on 'Security', check the option that says 'Block third-party and advertising cookies' and finally click 'Save'.  
  
For all other browsers and platforms please consult your help guides.

**Further information**  
If you'd like to learn more about cookies in general and how to manage them, why not visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) (opens in a new window - please note that we can't be responsible for the content of external websites).
